Some important things that men like this,
how can we add modern red color,
so let's start with the station
job, we discussed that if we do the
whole event on a bank holiday, then we will
quote from any authorized cigarette,
after this if you take reverse, if you are free, then
we are going to shout the bathroom below it,
today because I have stolen airplane
mode 38.00, especially you will
see some consolidation here,
if we just do it, then general, there
is still a celebration, but
considering the trend of the global market, tomorrow
you can see some short covering from here,
first of all, if we talk about Nifty today,
after a long time of syrup, today you will see a search, increase their words,
now here and in the last few minutes,
we will look at short covering, because of that
we have gone to the day log key and shown a question,
if we consider the
vibrator and open interest here, then the
open interest of the admit dog tells us that
That here above 80
we have a fresh close and vane. So
looking at this, if you want to see the short comings off tomorrow,
you can select the
strongest product which you want to like.
So here for this
we have to wait for it to go back to 1000
and the option channel is after that,
here it is
trying to turn on 7800. Those
Indian who have
taken debit/credit here, please tell them that a
little soft capil may come from here, but for
this we have to request 4020 important awards
again. For this,
let's go to 39518. Any
positional trader among the robbers can create an award
and install it on the side. What is the meaning, I will
tell you first here, if the 39th
can close below 60 for a minute, until we
do, then we can take any cut on the long side. This is
suicide, this
thing can be seen here. These are the
open interest which we
can see in the past because  A quick call above 5000 here
and that too call send and talk on the back foot, then
39518 is ours which is going to
act as support, so if
you see any sorry from this ribbon, then
you can clear 39518 quote from here apart from such option,
so let's see
those stars and the decision behind it
is appropriate, for this always update and
share, tell me the first stock which comes
here and today
after the results permission, we
see a shortage of used staff
and after continuous only, there is only one important thing in the stock, the
breakout which happened
on the basis of the earth period center shows us the added support for, so
guys here
because its support of the soil has been
broken and due to continuous,
we can collect this treatment and diet in future also,
if you
can do this for stock monitor, then you can consider
a target of at least ₹50 from the current levels back
and for that
Burn while making profit in the above a pune, those who
should give limit to other stocks, tell me here
you have to work on trading on this,
if you will see a consolidation of 500 in Nifty and that soil, then
you will
puncture this topic, so the guide chop is
TVS Motor Stock, the playlist video here,
after a refinement above that level, we have a strong
off side, see here today,
dominant leg, now on the
skin, what will we do,
and you are the
subscriber
staff, I am here
because
if you liked the video, then
definitely like and share it and subscribe to the channel
because this motivates us and
we will keep bringing such updates for you first, the
third topic comes here,
after YouTube, a consolidation and quality filled
fiction, we are talking about it,
here on Gujarat Gas, the
operating profit margin here has
come down significantly and if we
play it, then in the truck you will see
a user drive from here in the next few periods  It
can be seen, so if we look at the tips of some insiders, then in the
last few
periods, a strong bear was
doing this treatment here and today he did not come to the office, he
saw Gurjars below a pick and then
you can expect a similar trend in the stock in future as well.
Now if
you have any kind of questions below the phase here in the stock, then
you can also see that after which you will see 582 and
5.75. By
subscribing to Star Plus,
whatever features
and stocks come,
after taking a lot for the last few days, you can
see it on one side here and
because of its and that positive reason, this
side is loot, due to short covering, it
takes it higher, definitely see type here
106520, if we stitch this level here, then
you can write the stoploss of
MP exit up to six hundred seventy five or six hundred one inch,
Star Plus, you have to write the
stoploss of at least one question, you
yourself Dwivedi, that you are going to unite for your test,
so guys in this video  That's all
for all of you and if you have
n't joined our delivery yet then you will
definitely join, you will find the link
in the description below and
for additions and position updates you have to
join our group
memberships which you will see planted below till then
thank you so much and
accused
that a
[Music]